Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
[Rand groans]
Your father's in danger.
Special Agent Billie Rand. FBI.
I don't talk to cops.
They're gonna kill him. Lucky.
[spoon clinking loudly]
Here's what I know.
Priscilla buys gas. wholesale.
She doesn't pay state taxes.
She then resells it
through shell companies for full price.
That's what I know.
What I don't have is anything
that connects her to that scam.
What she's very good at
is making other people take the fall.
Guess who the fall guy is.
I have enough to put Cary and John away
for the next ten years.
If that were true.
you would have done it already.
Unless there's a reason that I haven't.
Okay. so you only want Priscilla.
And Whittaker.
And I know you want the same thing.
You don't know anything about what I want.
I know that before this.
you and your father
were strictly small-time.
I know that you know that your daddy
is in over his head with Priscilla.
And I know that you wanna get her out
of his life.
So what would you have me do?
Help me take the bull's-eye
off your father's back.
Putting Priscilla behind bars
may be the only way to keep him safe.
You can't guarantee that.
No. But I can keep him out of prison…
if you help me take her down.
I can't.
No.
You sure?
Yeah. I've been chasing Priscilla.
but I've been watching you.
And all your life. you've been…
[sighs]
…playing the hand you were dealt.
This is an opportunity for you
to get out of this shit.
To play with a fresh deck.
What about Cary?
Depends on how deep he goes.
Full immunity.
For my dad and for Cary or else no deal.
Girl.
You ask for a lot.
So do you.
[theme song playing]
You're alive.
Good for you.
- Lucky.
- Give me the seed phrase.
Lucky. you gotta listen to me.
No. The seed phrase. Please.
Lucky.
Listen. I need to explain. all right?
Can I… Can I… Can I explain?
Don't!
[groans]
[Cary] Fuck.
[breathes shakily]
No. I don't want your fucking ice.
Sorry. I knew you would find me.
I just didn't think it would be this soon.
[chuckles] I think we're
experiencing time a little differently.
Okay. well. whatever happened. I'm sorry.
I understand. okay?
What? Don't… Don't do that.
- No.
- What?
Don't do the thing that you do
where you try and appease me
before you even know
what the fuck you did.
- I know what the fuck I did.
- Oh. no. you don't.
- Lucky…
- You made me a fucking mark. Cary!
- No. that's not what happened.
- Bullshit!
- I didn't have a choice.
- Bullshit again!
Can I explain myself?
No. I don't wanna hear it.
I know you don't.
but I think you fucking need to right now.
No. I know you've had as much time
to rehearse for this moment
as I've spent picturing it.
So I am sure you've
got a great story loaded up
and ready to go. but I really don't want...
I will hit you again!
Okay. Fuck.
Maybe go for a softer area this time.
Are you seriously trying
to be fucking charming right now?
I'm not. This is hard for me too. okay?
Of course. this is hard for you.
Yes. let's make this about you…
- That's not what I meant.
- …and your obvious misery.
I was terrified. Cary.
Okay? I didn't know
whether I had to be hating you
or grieving you
or fucking somehow saving you.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- Don't!
You know. at first. I thought that maybe
something had been done
to both of us. right?
Like maybe we were both drugged.
and you were hurt or worse.
and I was gonna have to spend the rest of
my life never knowing what had happened.
But after a while. I realized
that the only possibility
that I could actually accept
was that you were dead.
Because at least if you were dead then
that means that you did not do this to me.
But here you are alive and well
in a fucking beach house.
and you did do this to me.
[Rand] We've got a hit on the plates and
IDed Masterson at the house in La Jolla.
We've got local cops moving in.
but I'm requesting all federal agents
in the area.
[dispatcher] All available units.
report back to the station
to assist an FBI fugitive task force.
Please indicate then switch to four.
Fugitive task force?
Do you think that's him?
- We'll know soon enough.
- [sighs]
What a mess.
We've cleaned up worse.
Remember Temple City?
Oh. God. I think I blocked that.
The point is. we walked out of there.
You and I have walked out a lot of places
that no one should have walked out of.
Yes. but this is Cary. okay.
He's not like us.
- I still have to kill spiders for him.
- [chuckles]
Drive faster. please.
[engine revving]
I know how this looks. okay?
And part of the reason it looks that way
is because it is that way.
I can't deny that.
And I'm not gonna sit here
and try and excuse what I've done.
But I've had some time to think about it.
and even now…
even now. standing here with you.
I don't know if I would have been able
to do things any differently. okay?
And believe me. however much you hate me
right now in this moment.
it doesn't even… it doesn't fucking
compare to how much I hate myself for it.
I think you might
be underestimating me. honey.
- Don't say that.
- Well. I don't know who you are.
- Yes. you do. You know me.
- Cary. no. I don't.
The person I know wouldn't do this.
You're the only person
who's ever known me. Lucky.
Clearly.
Look. I made a mistake.
I know I made a mistake.
But you're not gonna stand there
and convince me
that what we have isn't real. okay?
I fell in love with you
two seconds after I saw you.
- And asking you to marry me...
- Okay. so when did the lies start?
- What?
- Well. was it before the wedding?
- No. That was all real.
- After the wedding?
I know it might be difficult
to pinpoint an exact date.
but I'm just trying to get a general
picture of when my life became a lie...
She was going to kill you!
My darling boy.
Hello. Mother.
- Look at you.
- Hello.
[chuckles]
[Priscilla clicks tongue] Oh.
Oh. I missed you.
- [chuckles]
- [sighs]
Come on.
I would have visited you if you'd let me.
Oh. I couldn't let you see me in there.
[chuckles]
Yeah. I just really hate
that you were in there and not Wayne.
It's okay.
It's not.
[chuckles] Well. listen.
All that matters is I am here now.
[chuckles] Here. sit down.
How did you get out?
Uh. good behavior.
Wayne's lawyers?
What's in it for him?
Well. it's been brought to my attention
that there's some money missing.
Does that have something to do with me?
Well. John's been stealing
from me for years.
Skimming.
And the only person
who knows where that money is.
is that little girlfriend of yours.
- Wife.
- What?
You're married?
You didn't tell me?
You wouldn't see me.
Listen.
I know it's been hard. okay?
You had to do what you had to do
to survive.
But I'm out now.
And we're gonna get our business in order
and everything is gonna go back to normal.
I love her. Mom.
Oh. come on. What happened to you?
I'm gone for two years.
I-I don't even recognize you.
Well. I'm happy. Maybe that's why
you don't recognize me.
- Oh. you're not happy.
- I am.
Look at you. You're bored.
You're working minimum wage
and playing house with that little girl.
You're capable of so much more.
It's a nice life.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Is that what you want?
A nice life?
Man. you got a seat at the table.
Wayne is ready to bring you into the fold.
Wayne does not…
Wayne does not give a shit about me. okay?
And he definitely does not
give a shit about you.
Yeah. you bring in that money.
I promise you that's gonna change.
I'm not doing this shit for Wayne. Mom.
No. no. do it for yourself.
I'm giving you a gift here.
This is a chance at a better life.
What. like yours?
You just got out of prison. Mom.
Prison.
I-I-I love that we're having
this conversation right now. I love it!
Look. [sighs]
Look. you could do it with the girl. okay?
[scoffs]
All you have to do is get her
to bring it to me.
And then we're done.
You can live your life.
You know. you can…
move to Fresno and work at Starbucks.
I don't know. Whatever the fuck you want.
So you're saying no?
- I am.
- Okay. why?
I'm in love. Mom.
I'm in love. and I know
you wouldn't understand that.
So you're sacrificing everything
for a girl who is lying to you?
What are you talking about?
That girl that
you're so madly in love with.
You were busted by the fucking feds. Mom.
Yeah. how do you think that happened?
- Huh?
- No. Bullshit.
That's bullshit. okay? Her father
went down in that bust. all right.
So did she. right?
They took her away in cuffs. right?
Yet she was never charged.
never even interrogated.
No. no. no.
Because she was barely involved. Mom.
She was an accessory. Cary.
With knowledge of the organization.
And they let her walk.
Did it never fucking occur to you
to ask her why?
Are you really so fucking naive?
Oh.
Lucky knows where my money is
and you're gonna bring it to me.
[Cary sighs]
You know what Wayne's gonna do to me
if I don't bring him that money?
Are you really gonna let that happen?
Mom. [sighs]
This is my life.
There was a time
that meant something to you.
You won't do it for me.
your fucking mother.
Do it for your wife if you love her
the way you say you do.
Because you know what happens to her
if I have to handle this myself.
Okay? And you didn't think
to tell me any of this?
[scoffs] Tell you? Tell you?
- Are you fucking kidding me right now?
- Okay. Okay. We…
- Don't turn it around right now.
- Don't turn it around?
You worked with the feds
and you didn't tell me.
You're the reason she went to prison.
They were already on to her.
- Bullshit.
- [stammers] I had no choice.
When I said that two minutes ago.
you said. "Bullshit."
Well. when you said it. it was.
You can tell yourself whatever you want.
but you know I'm right.
You lied to me.
I wanted to tell you…
- But you didn't. did you?
- But...
You had years to tell me the truth.
Years.
The whole time we were married.
every time I talked to you about my mom.
you never thought to mention
that you were the one who sold her out.
- I-I couldn't.
- And now you come in here
trying to claim some type
of moral high ground
- telling me that I'm the one...
- Everything I did. I did for us. okay?
I was trying to protect us.
I was trying to protect you.
Leaving me for dead in a hotel room
is not protecting me. Cary!
I told you. if I didn't bring her
that money she was going to kill you.
And she still will.
What part of this
do you not understand. okay?
She was. is. always will be bad news.
You're just too close to see it.
- She would not have stopped…
- Whoa.
…until she got us all killed.
and I had to do something about it.
I was too close?
How the fuck is that any different
from you and John?
Well. because my dad's not a gangster.
Think you might be splitting hairs there.
You know what?
Do not talk about my father.
Don't talk… Are you fucking kidding me?
Are you kidding me?
This was all him.
He did this.
He fucked us
the moment he stole from Wayne.
The whole reason
we're even in this position right now
is because of him.
It's him.
And even now.
you're still too blind to see it.
[sighs]
[Rand] I need black and whites
at Ocean and Magnolia.
a hundred yards from the house.
Do not engage.
I repeat. do not engage.
Don't let the suspects see the cars.
Only intercept.
Only intercept if he tries to flee.
So there was never a cargo plane
to fly us out of Vegas. no Dominica.
From the moment we decided
to take the money.
you knew you were gonna take it from me.
I knew the day before we left.
after I saw my mom.
The night you couldn't sleep.
Figures.
So why didn't you…
give her the money?
I don't know.
You don't know?
[Cary] I was trying to keep you safe.
It really is beautiful.
[Cary] I didn't want to betray you.
It really is.
Okay. I was torn.
To our old life.
[sighs]
I mean. I'd just had
the worst night of my life.
but I did what I was supposed to do.
Um…
Made it there. drop with the money.
It was at this roadside diner
off the highway and I was about to go in.
trade cars. execute the plan.
she would have the money
and it would all be over.
And I was watching her
through the window of this diner
having coffee with Dutch.
calmly waiting for me
to deliver the money to her feet.
knowing without a doubt that I would do it
because she's her and I'm me.
and that's how it's been
my whole goddamn life.
And I'm…
I'm sitting in my car
and I can see her face from where I'm at.
And she…
she laughs.
[no audible dialogue]
No idea what she was laughing at.
but it didn't matter. It didn't matter.
She'd just destroyed the one thing
in my life that I loved.
and she was sitting there laughing.
[no audible dialogue]
And something in me. just. it…
I wasn't gonna be
her fucking pawn anymore.
I mean. I'd lived my entire life for her.
and in that moment. I just…
I hated everything about her.
So. I just… I ran.
Would've been nice if you'd had that
little epiphany before you fucked me over.
No shit.
- Could've come back for me. you know.
- I did come back.
I just… I couldn't get to you.
I was too late.
[Lucky] So you just kept going.
[Cary] God.
There was nothing I could do.
Okay. I knew you'd get out.
but I had to do something with the money.
Thank you.
[Lucky] So. what did you think
was gonna happen to me?
- I told you…
- Yeah. yeah. yeah. yeah. I know.
I would "get out." Great. But after that?
Like. what did you think your mother
was going to do to me?
I thought she would come after me.
She knew I had the money.
so I figured you'd be safe...
She put me in a fucking trunk. Cary.
- Fuck.
- Yes.
She thought we were in it together.
She was gonna have her men take me apart
to find out where you were.
Okay. I swear to God… I swear to God.
I didn't think she would come after you.
Well. yeah. I guess she didn't think
you'd betray me either.
I should've realized. I just didn't have
enough time to think it through.
That's where I fucked up. She knew
you were the one that put her away.
so of course she was gonna come after you.
That's my fault.
Let's try to figure out why.
Why'd you do it?
Why'd you work with the feds?
Because I couldn't find another way
to protect us.
So you just decided all our fates?
No. I did what I had to do.
Maybe Rand manipulated you.
Did you ever consider that?
- No.
- Why the hell not?
- Because I did not do it for Rand.
- Why'd you...
I did it for my father.
and I did it for you.
and you did what you did
for ten million dollars.
It was never about the money.
It was never about the money. Okay?
It was about you.
I love you.
- I know you still love me.
- No. I don't.
I don't believe you.
It's not a fucking choice.
Well. I don't care what you believe.
Don't say you don't love me.
I know when you're lying.
You know what? I am done
having this conversation with you.
Give me the seed phrase.
- No.
- No?
No. I digitized the money so no one could
get their hands on it. including you.
- It's not yours.
- And it's not yours either.
And it's definitely not John's.
I didn't go through all this bullshit
just to give it to him.
Give it to me now.
You won't shoot me.
You drugged me. robbed me.
left me for dead.
and you have no fucking idea
what I've been through since then.
So you'll just have to
take my word for it when I say
that I will absolutely shoot you.
The problem with that
is the seed phrase is in here.
so if you shoot me it dies with me.
Well. who said anything about killing you?
I dare you.
[pounding on door]
[Rand. on bullhorn]
Cary Masterson. it's the FBI.
We know you're in there.
Come out slowly
with your hands in the air.
I'm gonna reach in my pocket.
Don't do anything crazy.
- [pounds on door]
- [Rand] I don't want anybody to get hurt.
Don't make us come in there.
You were always a better driver.
We're going in.
[agent] Living room. clear.
Kitchen. clear.
First floor. clear.
[Rand] What the hell?
What the hell?
Blue Bronco! Blue Bronco! Go. go. go!
- [agent] Let's move.
- It's Lucky.
It's fucking Lucky.
Put every unit on them.
Block the freeways.
Don't let your eyes
in the sky give them an inch!
- [sirens blaring]
- [tires screech]
[Cary grunts]
For a second. I thought you were
actually gonna shoot me.
Yeah. I still might.
- [Cary] Car. Car.
- [Lucky speaks indistinctly]
Yes. I have eyes!
- Whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa.
- Shit. Shit. shit. shit. shit. shit.
- We're on the opposite side of the road…
- I know that.
…Lucky. come on.
[helicopter whirring]
What?
- Turning left.
- Oh. shit. [grunts]
[dispatcher] High rate of speed.
Medium traffic growing dense.
Approaching La Jolla Village Drive.
- Where is she headed?
- Shit.
Roberts. send four black and whites
- to the Mexican border.
- [Roberts] On it.
You think she'd really try to
cross the border with this much heat?
I don't wanna find out the hard way.
[dispatcher] Traffic is growing dense.
suspects will be blocked in.
Let's go. They've got no way out.
All right. we need to get off this road
and head south towards Mexico.
We? I'm not going anywhere with you.
Okay. Well. right now
that's really not an option.
[exclaims]
Fuck! You're gonna get us killed.
Do you wanna get out?
I can drop you off right here.
[Cary] I'm not asking you to forgive me.
but right now we both want the same thing.
I just need you to trust me
for about ten minutes. okay?
Well. we can't go anywhere
until we lose this helicopter.
[Cary] Yeah. and how the hell
are we gonna do that?
- How the hell are we gonna do that?
- I'm thinking.
- Well. what are you thinking. Lucky?
- Just trust me.
[dispatcher 2] Air One to ground.
we pulled the wrong vehicle
from under the overpass.
Negative visual on the blue Bronco.
Repeat. we lost visual.
[agent] Move in.
Passenger's side. check.
It's clear.
All right. where we going?
Somewhere we can blend in.
Roberts.
What the hell happened?
- [Roberts] They ditched the car.
- [Gates] No shit.
[radio chatter]
They're up there.
They're up there on foot.
I want every cop car
to circle topside and corral them.
- The suspects are on foot.
- They're not far.
Form a perimeter. Let's go!
Can I ask you something?
[sighs] Now's not really a good time.
John asked you to take the money for him.
Why'd you do it?
Our parents were locked up.
we had the life you always wanted.
you were happy. and then John calls
and you just give it all up for him?
- Well. they would've come for us anyway.
- Who?
Whittaker. Your mother.
They either would've thought
that I had something to do with it
or they would've used me
to get John to talk.
Either way. that life was over.
- Yeah. you wanna know what I think?
- Not really.
I think you don't know
how to say no to your dad.
[tires squeal]
You're together?
- [Lucky breathing heavily]
- Well. get in. We don't have time.
Honey. I can forgive you.
Just get in!
[sighs] Idiot.
- [pedestrian yelps]
- [person] Hey!
[panting]
- [grunting]
- [person] Asshole!
Excuse me! Please. you need to help me.
You see that man. he is chasing me.
I do not feel safe.
Please. I don't feel safe with him...
Just leave me alone.
[Lucky] Sir. I'm not safe.
[panting] Fuck was that?
[engine starts]
[engine revs]
[Gates] They've gotta be here.
If they're still on foot.
She could've lifted a car.
If that's the case. then we have no idea
what the fuck we're looking for.
We go inland.
There's a million different routes
that we can take there
and we'll just disappear.
You sure you don't wanna head south
and just wait at the border?
- Wait at the…
- Yes.
That's exactly
what they're expecting us to do.
I just think it's our quickest out. Lucky.
- Wait. what are you...
- Lucky.
- They looking?
- I don't know.
But don't look.
I said don't look. Cary.
Careful.
[sighs]
Okay. A million routes.
I don't know what that means.
We need to pick one.
I am clearly driving right now.
Can you just navigate for me. please?
- If you drive. we'll be driving all day.
- Fuck!
Oh. Jesus.
- [grunts]
- [Priscilla] That was them.
Okay. okay. okay. okay.
I'm just gonna do it.
- Shit. Shit. shit. shit. shit. shit.
- Whoa. Whoa.
- Fuck! No!
- Shit.
Get… Stay on them. Stay on them.
- Faster. Lucky. Come on!
- I'm trying. please. just…
- [Cary exclaims]
- [tires screech]
- Shit.
- [car horn honks]
Okay.
[sirens wailing]
Catch them on the other side.
Ah. we're fucked. We're fucked.
- Lucky. stop.
- Stop.
Holy shit!
This is crazy.
- Cary?
- I know.
I don't regret us.
Neither do I.
What are you doing?
Buying us some time.
Shit.
Fuck!
[grunts]
Cary?
[yelps]
[both grunting]
[no audible dialogue]
- It's over. Lucky.
- [panting]
Where's he going?
[Lucky panting]
Couldn't keep him out of it.
What? Wh… [pants]
- I'm sorry.
- No. wait. What are you talking about?
He was in deeper than I realized
and it was out of my hands.
No. no. no. You… You promised me.
I did what I could.
- [stammers] Sorry?
- I'm sorry.
No. You can't just do that.
It was out of your hands?
You used me!
- I'm sorry. Let's go.
- No.
Okay. wait. No. no. no.
You… you… you can't do that.
Okay? We had a deal.
You promised me! I helped you!
Do you understand that this is my life?
What is wrong with you? You are a liar!
[sobs] You lied to me!
[screaming. crying]
- [breathes heavily]
- [groans] They shot me.
- [coughs]
- Cary! [breathes heavily]
- [grunting]
- Oh. Cary. Cary. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. sorry. sorry. Hey. baby-baby.
Don't look down. Don't look down.
- Hey. look at me. Look at me.
- [grunts]
- Hey. Hey. it's okay. It's okay.
- [grunting]
Goddamn it.
It's okay.
It's-It's-It's-It's gonna be fine.
I think the gun was a bad choice.
- Hey. Hey. honey. Don't look at it.
- [panting]
Look at me. Hey. focus.
- Cary. I need you to focus.
- Yeah.
I need you to focus. Look at me.
Look at me. Breathe. baby. Breathe.
Yeah. there we go. There we go. honey.
It's gonna be fine. It's gonna be fine.
It's gonna be fine.
I think I'm gonna die.
No. honey. No. No. baby.
It's okay. It's okay.
Hey. Hey.
Cary? Cary?
[breathes heavily]
You… You were happy.
You were happy…
Cary?
Cary. open your eyes. Look at me.
Look at me. Cary! You can't leave me!
Cary!
Fucking wake up! You can't leave me.
[crying]
No!
[crying] Fucking wake up!
Come on!
[sniffs] Please.
[crying]
[approaching sirens]
[grunts]
- Wait.
- [Rand grunting. panting]
[Gates] Rand. wait!
[breathes shakily]
[panting]
- [Gates] Where did she go?
- [sirens wailing]
Rand!
- [Rand thuds]
- Officer down!
Rand! Hey.
[panting]
No!
No! My baby!
- No. you can't. You can't. Come on.
- No! Let me go. Let me go.
[sobbing] No! No!
No! No!
[wails]
[screams]
My baby!
["Into the Black" playing]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm